import { Topic } from '.'

export const reasoningSet3: Topic = {
    topic: 'Reasoning',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 20,
    totalScore: 200,
    totalTime: 1200,
    questions: [
      {
        question: `What comes next: 3, 6, 12, 24, ?`,
        choices: ['36', '48', '50', '46'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['48'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `If CAT = 3120, and DOG = 4157, what is GOD?`,
        choices: ['7514', '7451', '7415', '7541'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['7415'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which direction is opposite to South-East?`,
        choices: ['North-West', 'North-East', 'South-West', 'North'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['North-West'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Find the missing number: 2, 4, 7, 11, ?`,
        choices: ['16', '17', '15', '18'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['16'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Choose the odd one: Apple, Banana, Orange, Carrot`,
        choices: ['Apple', 'Banana', 'Orange', 'Carrot'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Carrot'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which number does not belong: 121, 144, 169, 196, 210`,
        choices: ['121', '144', '210', '169'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['210'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Select the related word: Fish : Water :: Bird : ?`,
        choices: ['Sky', 'Tree', 'Nest', 'Cage'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Sky'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `If 5 + 3 = 28, 4 + 2 = 18, what is 6 + 4 = ?`,
        choices: ['50', '60', '45', '48'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['48'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which figure is different: Square, Triangle, Circle, Hexagon`,
        choices: ['Square', 'Triangle', 'Circle', 'Hexagon'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Circle'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which number should replace the question mark? 10, 20, 40, ?, 160`,
        choices: ['60', '70', '80', '90'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['80'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Find the odd one out: Mango, Apple, Banana, Potato`,
        choices: ['Mango', 'Apple', 'Banana', 'Potato'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Potato'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Choose the pair with a similar relation: Eye : See`,
        choices: ['Ear : Hear', 'Nose : Eat', 'Hand : Walk', 'Tongue : Smell'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Ear : Hear'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `If 9 × 3 = 36 and 6 × 2 = 20, then 5 × 4 = ?`,
        choices: ['25', '30', '28', '26'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['30'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `What is the mirror image of the letter ‘L’?`,
        choices: ['ᒣ', '⅃', 'L', 'J'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['⅃'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `What comes next: 64, 32, 16, 8, ?`,
        choices: ['6', '4', '2', '1'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['4'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Odd one out: Fan, Light, Bulb, Chair`,
        choices: ['Fan', 'Light', 'Bulb', 'Chair'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Chair'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which does not belong to the group: Pen, Pencil, Eraser, Spoon`,
        choices: ['Pen', 'Pencil', 'Eraser', 'Spoon'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Spoon'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `If A = Z, B = Y, C = X, then DOG = ?`,
        choices: ['WLT', 'WOL', 'WLM', 'WLU'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['WLT'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Find the next in the pattern: 2, 3, 5, 8, 12, ?`,
        choices: ['15', '17', '18', '19'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['17'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Identify the missing letter: A, C, F, J, O, ?`,
        choices: ['R', 'S', 'U', 'V'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['U'],
        score: 10,
       
      }
    ]
  }
  